# MATTHEW C. MOYA

3116 164th ST SW| Lynnwood WA 98087 | C: 425.773.4447 | Matthewcmoya5@gmail.com

## **OBJECTIVE**

To fully transition from freelance Web Development/Bartending to a full time, all encompassing career in the Web Development world. Although all my listed work experience is bartending related, I have contributed to many web based projects and sites while emphasizing the importance of beautiful, semantic code.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Bartender, John Howie Steak; WA (January- Current) Supervisor: Tim Lodahl, Bar Manager

Consistently provide unmatched service at the number one steakhouse in Washington State.

Control liquor costs and counts with extensive inventory of rare spirits and wines.

Contributor to the creation of our ever changing cocktail list.

Lead Bartender, Manager, The Keg; WA (2008-2015) Supervisor: Nephi Ruff, General Manager

Awarded best bartender out of all Pacific Northwest Keg restaurants for the year 2011.

Trained and led staff of all levels on a day-to-day basis while monitoring and maintaining liquor counts and costs.

Personally saw to a healthy growth in business by acquiring a large number of regular guests.

Bartender, Server, Ocean Avenue Seafood; Santa Monica, CA (2012-2013) Supervisor: Brett Reed

Quickly progressed within the restaurant from server, to bartender and trainer.

Personally asked by superiors to move into a front of house Supervisor/Management role.

Handle large amounts of responsibilities simultaneously while maintaining a calm personable attitude.

Head Baker, Panera Bread; Lynnwood, WA (2005- 2008) Supervisor: Bryan Beck, Bakery Market Manager

Oversaw night operations and coordinated with the General Manager.

Trained and organized a strong team of bakers.

Raised the bar for bakers company wide as the youngest head baker in the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

Edmonds Community College on direct transfer agreement with the University of Washington.

### SKILLS/ CORE STRENGTHS

- Confident and charismatic public speaker.
- · Well practiced and accomplished in multi-tasking.
- Extensive knowledge of computers and programs.
- Personable demeanor and strong team player.
- Insatiable hunger for growth and success.
- Proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript.

## SPECIAL PROJECTS/VOLUNTEER WORK

Boys and Girls Club, Santa Monica, CA (2012-2013)

Lead and mentor kids ages 11-15 two days a week teaching them good values, morals, and healthy loving lifestyles.

Hopelink, Kirkland, WA (2010-2011)

Volunteered up to three days a week in a warehouse style food bank organizing and regulating product in preparation for distribution.

Woodstick, Seattle-Tacoma, WA (2003)

Had an active part in starting the first annual fundraiser to eradicate Polio which resulted in thousands of dollars earned and a Guinness World Record for most drummers playing in unison.

### **REFERENCES**

Max Brockman: maxbrockman453@gmail.com

Dean Shelton: deanshelton913@gmail.com